Federation of Ukrainian Student Organizations of America. Records, 1950-1966: A Finding Aid.
Records, 1950-1966.
- III. Ukrainian Student Clubs ([Boxes 3, 4, 5])
  - New York ([Box 4])
    - UASS at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Troy--photographs:, 1962-1963
      - Dypliak, Mykola, 1963
      - Freshman Orientation Week--Kobziar, Andrii, Ivan Durbak, Iaroslav Kindrachuk, and Jack Spivak, Sep. 1962
      - Freshman Orientation Week--Ukrainian display booth, Sep. 1962
      - International Christmas Festival, Dec. 1962
      - Members, c. 1962-1963
      - Members (A. Komar, R. Bilas, L. Zobniw, O. Bachinska, O. Halkewycz, O. Gogosha, O. Komar, Z. Ivanonko, W. Prybyla and M. Prybyla), Apr. 1962
      - Members (L. Zobniw, W. Prybyla, Z. Ivanonko, R. Bilas, O. Komar, O. Bachinska, O. Halkewycz, and M. Komar), Apr. 1962
      - Misc., 1963
      - Pre-Collegiate Conference, Mar. 1963
      - Tymchuk, Nadiia, 1963
      - Ukrainian exhibit, Apr. 1962
      - Ukrainian exhibit, Apr. 1962
      - Ukrainian exhibit--W. Prybyla, R. Bilas, and L. Zobniw, Apr. 1962
      - Zobniw, Lubomyr, n.d.
      - Zobniw, Lubomyr and Roksolana Bilas, Mar. 1963
      - Zobniw, Lubomyr and Tom Nelson, 1963
    - UASS at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Troy, 1963
    - Ukrainian students in Utica--photographs:, c. 1956-1957
      - Bureau of Reporters--Members (inc. Vol. Litynskyi and Ia. Lyktei), c. 1956-1957
      - Litynskyi, Volodymyr and Iaroslav Lyktei with Dean of Syracuse Univ.c. 1956-1957
      - Lyktei, Iaroslav, n.d.
      - Lyktei, Iaroslav and Italian student, c. 1956-1957
    - Ukrainian students in Utica, 1963
  - Ohio ([Boxes 4, 5])
    - Adam Kotsko Ukrainian-American Student Society (UASS) in Cleveland--correspondence (sent), 1952-1953 ([Box 4])
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland--misc., 1952-1959 ([Box 4])
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland, 1953 ([Box 4])
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland, 1953-1955 ([Box 4])
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland--photographs, 1953-1963
      - Battle of Kruty commemoration, n.d. ([Box 4])
      - Fur, Mariia, n.d.
      - Futei, Bohdan, n.d.
      - Halushchynskyi, Iurii, n.d.
      - Holubets, Daria, n.d.
      - Holubets, Zenon, n.d.
      - Hordiichuk, Marta, n.d.
      - Hrushkevych, Motriia, n.d.
      - Hrushkevych, Volodymyr, n.d.
      - International Students Club--Vrublivskyi, Osyp with other members, 1956
      - Kunash, Ihor, n.d.
      - Members, n.d.
      - Members with Lithuanian students' group, 1953
      - Muzychka, Liarissa and Iaroslav (wedding photo), May 3, 1958
      - Tarchanyn, Zinoviia, n.d.
      - Ukrainian exhibit (O. Vrublivskyi), 1956
      - Ukrainian Student Day--student delegation to Parma Mayor James Day's office, Jan. 29, 1963
      - Ukrainian Student Day--proclamation, Jan. 29, 1963
      - Volchuk, Orysia, n.d.
      - Volianyk, Marta, n.d.
      - Women's choir, n.d.
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland, 1955-1958 ([Box 4])
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland--misc., 1958-1960 ([Box 4])
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland--register of correspondence (rec.), 1960-1961 ([Box 4])
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland--misc., 1960-1961 ([Box 5])
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland--minutes, 1961-1962 ([Box 5])
    - Adam Kotsko UASS in Cleveland, 1963 ([Box 5])
    - Ukrainian Student Club (USC) at Ohio State University, Columbus, 1953-1954 ([Box 5])
    - USC at Ohio State University, Columbus, 1963 (inc. photographs of Olesnytska, Ksenia, n.d.; Pashyn, Bohdan, n.d.; Popel, Iurii, n.d.; and Shvabinskyi, Ostap, n.d.) ([Box 5])
    - Ukrainian Student Club (USC) at Kent State University--photographs:, 1957-1962
      - Fedorowycz, Tania, n.d. ([Box 5])
      - Fur, Mariia, n.d.
      - Halarewycz, Adrian, n.d.
      - Hrabets, Vira, n.d.
      - International Festival--Ukrainian exhibit, 1958
      - Iwanchuk, Iaroslav, n.d.
      - Iwanchuk, Marie, n.d.
      - Kulczyckyj, George, n.d.
      - Kuzmyn, Marie, n.d.
      - Malynowsky, Areta, n.d.
      - Markewycz, Melania, n.d.
      - Melnyk, Helen, n.d.
      - Members, 1962
      - Olinkewych-Kolodii, Areta, Jan. 1957
      - Olinkewych, Martha, n.d.
      - Popel, Martha, n.d.
      - Rakowsky, Roman, n.d.
      - Ratochko, Olga, n.d.
      - Sachno, Natalia, n.d.
      - Saluk, Kwitoslawa, n.d.
      - Steciak, Luba, n.d.
      - Taras Shevchenko exhibit, 1962
      - Tarchanyn, Zinoviia, n.d.
    - USC at Kent State University, 1960-1963 ([Box 5])
  - Pennsylvania ([Box 5])
    - Ukrainian Student Club (USC) in Philadelphia--minutes, 1952-1957
    - USC in Philadelphia--minutes, 1953-1954
    - USC in Philadelphia, 1953-1954
    - USC in Philadelphia--correspondence, 1953-1954
    - USC in Philadelphia--correspondence (rec.), 1954
    - USC in Philadelphia--correspondence (sent), 1955
    - USC in Philadelphia--correspondence, 1955-1956
    - USC in Philadelphia--correspondence, 1957
    - USC in Philadelphia--collection of speeches, 1958
    - USC in Philadelphia, 1958-1959
    - USC in Philadelphia--misc., 1958-1959
    - USC in Philadelphia--misc., 1959-1960
    - USC in Philadelphia, 1959-1960
    - USC in Philadelphia--photographs:, 1960-1963
      - Hasiuk, Andrii, n.d.
      - Hasiuk, Bohdan, n.d.
      - Members (I. Petyk, R. Shved, M. Petyk, and Iu. Savchak), n.d.
      - Members (O. Bohachevska, M. Petyk, V. Hnatiuk, V. Vanchytskyi, Z. Sochor, M. Tatomyr, A. Masiuk, and Iu. Hnatiuk), 1963
      - Members (O. Bohachevska, M. Petyk, V. Hnatiuk, V. Vanchytskyi, Z. Sochor, O. Poslushnyi, M. Tatomyr, A. Masiuk, and Iu. Hnatiuk), 1963
      - Members, n.d.
      - Procyk, Anna (at Ukrainian Ideological Congress, Philadelphia), May 1960
      - Savchak, Iurii, n.d.
      - Shved, Roman, n.d.
      - Tsikalo, Osyp, n.d.
      - Tsikalo, Osyp (at Ukrainian Student Days, Baltimore), Nov. 1958
      - Ukrainian Student Day--student delegation to Philadelphia Mayor J.H. Tate's office, Jan. 22, 1963
      - Ukrainian Student Ideological Congress in the U.S., 1960
      - University of Pennsylvania--Ukrainian literature class--professors and students (inc. Iurii Machuk, Hryhor Luzhnytskyi, and Bohdan Hasiuk) 1960
    - USC in Philadelphia, 1961-1962
    - USC in Philadelphia, 1961-1963
    - USC in Philadelphia, 1963
    - Ukrainian Student Club at Drexel Institute of Technology, Philadelphia, 1963 (inc. 2 photographs of Vira Shvabiak, Nov. 1958 and n.d.) Ukrainian Student Club at Temple University, Philadelphia--photographs:, 1961-1962
      - Government (P. Kotsiubailo, Z. Bernadyn, V. Vanchytskyi, M. Mazurak,and O. Nykorovych), 1961-1962
      - Members, 1961-1962
      - Vanchytskyi, Volodymyr, n.d.
    - Ukrainian Student Club in Pittsburgh, 1954
  - Washington DC ([Box 5])
    - Ukrainian Student Club in Washington DC--photographs, 1959-1963
      - Government (A. Bihun, V. Mayewsky, and V. Zabiaka), 1962
      - Government (A. Bihun, I. Markovskyi, V. Zabiaka, Iu. Kapustianskyi, and Ia. Oryshkywych), 1962
      - Government (Ia. Oryshkywych, M. Vitkovitsky, O. Jerschkowsky, A. Bihun, O. Subtelny, and I. Vitkovitsky), 1962
      - Kapustianskyi, Iurii, n.d.
      - Kozak, Adrian, 1960
      - Lomacky, Oles, n.d.
      - Mayewsky, Volodymyr Y., n.d.
      - Members (V. Mayewsky, N. Pylypets, P. Krul, S. Stetsura, ?
      - P. Odarchenko, O. Jerschkowsky, and O. Lomacky), 1959
      - Members, Feb. 1962
      - Members, Oct. 1962
      - Members (O. Diachok, O. Kravets, Ia. Oryshkywych, A. Bihun, L. Protsinskyi, and L. Karpyn), 1962
      - Members, 1962
      - Members, 1963
      - Oryshkywych, Iaromyr, n.d.
      - Presidents (V. Mayewsky, 1958-1960; O. Jerschkowsky, 1960-1961; and A. Bihun, 1961-), 1962
    - Ukrainian Student Club (USC) in Washington DC, 1960-1962
    - USC in Washington DC, 1963
  - Wisconsin
    - Ukrainian Academic Club in Madison, 1953-1954
- IV. Member Societies ([Box 5])
  - Zarevo--Cleveland branch, 1953-1954, 1963-1964
  - Zarevo--New York branch, 1959-1964
  - Zarevo--misc., 1960-1961
  - Zarevo--Central Executive in the USA--announcements, 1960-1963
  - Zarevo--Philadelphia branch, 1960-1964
  - Zarevo--Central Executive in the USA--announcements, 1961-1963
  - Zarevo--press clippings, 1961-1963
  - Zarevo--Central Executive in the USA--correspondence, 1961-1964
  - Zarevo--Chester, PA branch, 1962
  - Zarevo--Oleh Olzhych Society in Philadelphia, 1962-1963
  - Zarevo--Allentown, PA branch, 1963
  - Zarevo--Baltimore branch, 1963-1965
  - Zarevo--Newark branch, 1964
  - Zarevo--re. publication of "Ukrainskyi nationalizm", 1964-1965
  - Zarevo--misc., 1965
- V. Publications ([Box 6])
  - A. SUSTA
    - (Box 6)
    - Biuleten' (New York), 1953-1959
    - Istorychnyi narys (Baltimore), 1961
    - Pre-Collegiate Information Bulletin (Troy, NY), 1962-1963
    - Students'ke zhyttia: zhurnal seredn'oshkil'noi referentury SUSTA, 1966
    - Students'ke zhyttia: informatyvnyi i literaturno-mystets'kyi zhurnal, 1967
  - B. Member clubs and societies
    - Rozbudova derzhavy: biuleten' Zareva (Montreal), 1951-1953
    - Lystok druzhby: vyd. OUSTNS "Zarevo" (Chicago-Montreal), 1950-1961
    - Novyi svit: zhurnal prysv'iachenyi ukrains'kii students'kii problematytsi (Philadelphia), 1954
    - The Ukrainian-American Student News: A Quarterly (Cleveland), 1954
    - Rozbudova derzhavy: biuleten' Zareva (Cleveland), 1954-1958
    - Visti Ukrains'koho Students'koho Arkhivu-Muzeiu (Baltimore), 1960-1962
    - Student: orhan Ukrains'koi students'koi hromady u Filiadel'fii (Philadelphia), 1960-1963
    - Lystok TUSM-ivtsia (Detroit), 1961
    - Tri-City Ukrainian American Student Newsletter (Troy, NY), 1962
    - Visnyk ukrains'koho studenta: hazetka Ukrains'koho Studentstva m. Niu Iork ta okolyts' (Newark), 1964
    - Obizhnyk: Zarevo (New York), 1965-1966
    - Vezhi: orhan t-va Zarevo im. Oleha Ol'zhycha (Philadelphia), 1966
    - New York City Ukrainian Student Hromada Newsletter, 1969
- VI. Unprocessed materials ([Box 7])